<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[think: a commentary on experiences ]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[think: a commentary on experiences ]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2016 21:43:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can You See The International Space Station From Earth]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Can You See The International Space Station From Earth</h1><p>Advances in clean tech, renewable energy and sustainability initiatives will begin to reduce our reliance on traditional sources of power generation. Instead most of our energy needs could come from micro-scale renewable power generators. Breakthroughs in how researchers think about maintaining homeostasis and wellness will lead to new ways in how physicians diagnose and treat diseases. The sharing economy will expand to all touch points of daily life, where people will care less about outright ownership but rather shifts to concern about memberships and the quality of experiences provided along the way. Perhaps after establishing some sense of permanence and privacy of place, the spaces where we live will soon be populated by shared commodities based on our stage of life, professional and personal needs, why even bother to buy kitchen appliances, utensils, furniture, work clothes, casual wear and more when these can all be allocated to fit your needs. Could this create a new gap between the makers and consumers? Would this highly customized level of specificity help eliminate fear and worry about the most basic of living necessities or would it just serve to highlight the inequality of a small but emerging class of nouveau entrepreneurs amidst the masses of consumerism.  I still think the economic success of nations is going to be measured by the levels of advancements made in their respective fields of research and development and the resulting implementation through startups. Increasingly, conflicts are going to be issues of cyber security in gaining access to the masses, especially in wrangling control of the messaging and narrative in experiences. Specialized groups will still persist in seeking access to research insights and emerging technologies in a bid to gain the upper hand.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3c4b335bb6096767060833588ea0b89f1fcae934.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>undefinede3bc435e-af12-443b-b03b-9584993797e3/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e3bc435e-af12-443b-b03b-9584993797e3</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2016 21:43:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>